What is that?
這什麼鬼？
Well,
ㄜ...
I just thought it would be good to start with like,
我只是覺得...
a quote or something.
來段口白當開場白好像不錯...
Don't...., get rid of it, Idiot.
別...快跳過，白痴。
Ladies and gentlemen, hello welcome to the Wednesday
女士們先生們，歡迎來到[蛋和麻雀]
night open mic at the Egg and Sparrow
週三素人歡唱時間
we've a very special treat for you this evening,
今晚我們有非常特別的表演呈現給您，
a chap giving his debut performance,
是一位小夥子的首次亮相！
so please put your hands together and
所以請讓
welcome onto the stage.... Mr Tom Moody.
我們一同鼓掌歡迎 Tom Moody 先生
I'm Tom Moody.....
我是 Tom Moody
And... Well. What?
ㄜ...怎樣？
Well, we can't both tell this..
嗯...我們不能一直同時說
Absolutely, let me,
當然不行，我來。
I'm Tom Moody and this was the moment I knew for sure
我是Tom然後這是我期待已久的一刻
I was a deluded fool with no tal....
我一直是個笨蛋並且毫...
NO , that's not true... I am Tom Moody
才、才不是這樣！我是Tom,
and I've always loved making music.
我從小就愛製作音樂
even as a little boy me and my cousin Steve would
還是小男孩的時候我和我表弟Steve
get together and make recordings of our songs....
就會一起把我們的歌都錄下來
Oh please, the only thing Steve and me
最好是啦！Steve和我
ever recorded is ourselves farting.
唯一錄過的就是我們的放屁聲
Other than mum's affair with the ice cream man,
除了我媽跟賣冰淇淋的搞曖昧以外
my childhood was entirely unremarkable.
我的童年實在沒有值得炫耀的事
I was a dull and talentless child, I thank god that
我就是個沉悶又沒有才能的小孩，
dad was there to rescue me from the last shambles
我跟Steve捅了一個大爛攤
that me and Steve made of playing live
我真的很感謝我爸救了我們的現場演出
Were the... the, ... witches of ...Halloween oooo ,
在萬...萬聖節 嗚～～嗚～～
ooo, the.... scaryest you've ever seen,
你看過最可....可怕的女巫
now to the G,
現在G調 G!
we creep, cree....
我們可...可怕...
TO THE G CHORD!
是G!!!
oh for goodness sake, give it to me...
算了我來！把它給我！
we creep up in the night
我們藏在黑暗中
and give you such a FRIGHT!.....
要讓你嚇一跳！
We are the witches of Halloween...
我們是萬聖節的女巫們...
Yes, but, we were ill prepared that time
對但是當時我們沒有準備好
So, what's, that
剛剛那是什麼鳥
We've had 32 years of practice since then,
在32年的練習
we can turn this around....
以後我們扳回了...
I don't want to turn.....
我不想要...
Steve's the best keyboard player
Steve變成很棒的鍵盤手！
since flipping... Stevie wonder...
比史提夫汪達還強...
Are you joking...
你在開玩笑...
Lets make it Big...
我們把它講厲害一點
No!
別這樣！
What about David Bowie?
那大衛·鮑伊呢？
What about David Bowie!
大衛·鮑伊怎樣？
We could really rock them this time!
我們這次真的可以很酷炫！
It never sounded like this...
我們從沒有這麼厲害好嗎...
This is ridiculous...
這太愚蠢了...
We don't have a guitar like that....
我們才沒有那種吉他！
There were never any strings...
我們的一根弦都沒有！
There was no one playing drums!
沒有鼓聲！
We never had backing singers...
我們才沒有背景合音呢！
and Steve doesn't wear leopard skin pants.
而且Steve是不穿豹紋緊身褲的
That's the thing about talent,
天賦這種事情
you've either got it, or you've not...
有就是有，沒有就沒有
Boring, in fact it's not just boring it's sad,
無聊，其實不只無聊，
you actually inspire sadness in people,
你很慘，你讓別人也覺得悲慘
you bring people down....
你令人沮喪...
Moron, utter moron
智障， 超智障的
Ha! Ha,You should be ashamed,
哈哈，你應該感到羞愧
Why would anybody want to hear
為什麼沒人想聽？
SHUT UP!
不要吵了！！！
I told you this was pointless, ruined it...
我早說了這毫無意義
Shut up, please just shut up, or I am going to
閉嘴，拜託你閉嘴，不然我就要...
Oh yeah, what you going to what?
喔是嗎？你要怎樣阿？
I'm going to...
我要...
Get off me.
離開我！
You!
是你！
Tom,I didn't know...
Tom...我真的不知道
Tom?
What is it Tom?
Tom你怎麼了？
I don't want us to sing.
我不希望我們唱歌
Why?
為什麼？
People will think we're stupid and boring.
人們會覺得我們又笨又無聊
Well, I don't think we're stupid and boring,
嗯，我不覺得我們又笨又無聊阿
and we don't have to do it for them,
而且我們不需要為了他們唱
we can just do it for us.
我們可以只為了自己唱阿
Do we have to sing the witches of Halloween?
我們一定要唱萬聖節的女巫嗎？
We don't ever have to sing the witches of Halloween.
我們永遠都不用唱萬聖節女巫。
Ok
Like a bird, is born with a song,
像枝頭的鳥，生來就帶著一首歌
and like a song, wants to be sung...
而像一首歌，生來就該被歌唱